Wilson Kiggundu

Senior Software Engineer at Laboremus Uganda Ltd

wilson@schoolmaster.co.ug

Summary

I am an accomplished web applications developer. My main technologies of expertise include ASP.NET MVC, C#, PHP, Python, Javascript, CSS3, Bootstrap, Foundation, jQuery, SQL Server, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB.

I am a certified Data Scientist with knowledge in Excel, PowerBI, Machine Learning, R programming language, statistics, predictive analysis, Azure Machine Learning Studio.

I use Visual Studio, Android Studio, Netbeans, Eclipse, TeamCity, JIRA, Asana, Trello, Workbench, Adobe Creative Suite, PHP Storm, PyCharm

Experience

Senior Software Engineer

June 2013 - Present

Senior Software Engineer

June 2013 - Present

Writing sofware, project management, team coordination, print management, technical lead, quality analyst, tester

Senior Software Developer at Laboremus Oslo AS

August 2013 - October 2013 (2 months)

Developing software solutions mainly for the financial sector both for local and international clients

Chief Web Developer

June 2012 - June 2013 (1 year)

I am the Lead Developer for all the Web Applications developed by SchoolMaster Solutions

Systems Specialist

June 2011 - August 2012 (1 year 2 months)

Part of my assignments were developing custom software solutions for clients as well as systems administration task

Education

Makerere University

BSc Electrical Engineering, Computer Systems Networking and Telecommunications, 2007 - 2011

Old Kampala SS

Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics, Economics, 2005 - 2006

Wilson Kiggundu

Senior Software Engineer at Laboremus Uganda Ltd

wilson@schoolmaster.co.ug



Contact Wilson on LinkedIn